Joaquín Erlbaun /

Senior Associate

Practice Area: Tax Law

joaquin.erlbaun@ocl.cl

Joaquín has focused on Tax Law and is head of the tax litigation and dispute area. His education, complemented by his work experience in the public and private sector, have given him proven, successful experience in defending domestic and foreign clients before the tax authorities, the Treasury General of the Republic, Office of Accountability and specialty courts, as well as the Court of Appeals and Supreme Court.

WORK HISTORY

2018 - present / Ovalle Consejeros Legales

2017 - 2018 / Cuevas Abogados

2011 - 2016 / Ernst & Young

2009 - 2011 / Internal Revenue Service of Chile

2007 - 2009 / Deloitte

EDUCATION

Leadership and Management Courses, Harvard Extension School, 2014. LL.M., concentration in Tax Law, University of Chile, 2011.

B.A. in Legal and Social Sciences, Pontifical Catholic University of Chile. Admissions: 2004.

PUBLICATIONS

- New Tax Regimes in Chile, Pragma
- No New Taxes, Just a Slogan or Viable in Reality. Pragma

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English